Guide to the Archives Union File Part 2, Section 2: Boxes 66-129 1872-1976
Archives Union File Part 2, Section 2: Boxes 66-129
- The Tailor, 1912-1914 (Box 128, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: The Tailor, 1912; Publication (Box 128, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.23:no.2 (1912: Sept.)
  - Item 3: The Tailor, 1912; Publication (Box 128, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.23:no.3 (1912: Oct.)
  - Item 4: The Tailor, 1912; Publication (Box 128, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.23:no.4 (1912: Nov.)
  - Item 5: The Tailor, 1912; Publication (Box 128, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.23:no.5 (1912: Dec.)
  - Item 6: The Tailor, 1913; Publication (Box 128, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.23:no.6 (1913: Jan.)
  - Item 7: The Tailor, 1913; Publication (Box 128, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.23:no.7 (1913: Feb.)
  - Item 8: The Tailor, 1913; Publication (Box 128, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.23:no.8 (1913: Mar.)
  - Item 9: The Tailor, 1913; Publication (Box 128, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.23:no.9 (1913: Apr.)
  - Item 10: The Tailor, 1913; Publication (Box 128, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.23:no.10 (1913: May)
  - Item 11: The Tailor, 1913; Publication (Box 128, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.23:no.11 (1913: June)
  - Item 12: The Tailor, 1913; Publication (Box 128, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.23:no.12 (1913: July)
  - Item 13: The Tailor, 1913; Publication (Box 128, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.24:no.1 (1913: Aug.)
  - Item 14: The Tailor, 1913; Publication (Box 128, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.24:no.2 (1913: Sept.)
  - Item 15: The Tailor, 1913; Publication (Box 128, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.24:no.3 (1913: Oct.)
  - Item 16: The Tailor, 1913; Publication (Box 128, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.24:no.4 (1913: Nov.)
  - Item 17: The Tailor, 1913; Publication (Box 128, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.24:no.5 (1913: Dec.)
  - Item 18: The Tailor, 1914; Publication (Box 128, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.24:no.6 (1914: Jan.)
  - Item 19: The Tailor, 1914; Publication (Box 128, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.24:no.7 (1914: Feb.)
  - Item 20: The Tailor, 1914; Publication (Box 128, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.24:no.8 (1914: Mar.)
  - Item 21: The Tailor, 1914; Publication (Box 128, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.24:no.9 (1914: Apr.)
  - Item 22: The Tailor, 1914; Publication (Box 128, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.24:no.10 (1914: May)
  - Item 23: The Tailor, 1914; Publication (Box 128, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.24:no.11 (1914: June)
  - Item 24: The Tailor, 1914; Publication (Box 128, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.24:no.12 (1914: July)
- The Tailor, 1914-1915 (Box 129, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: The Tailor, 1914; Publication (Box 129, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.25:no.1 (1914: Aug. 4)
  - Item 2: The Tailor, 1914; Publication (Box 129, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.25:no.2 (1914: Aug. 11)
  - Item 3: The Tailor, 1914; Publication (Box 129, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.25:no.3 (1914: Aug. 18)
  - Item 4: The Tailor, 1914; Publication (Box 129, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.25:no.4 (1914: Aug. 25)
  - Item 5: The Tailor, 1914; Publication (Box 129, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.25:no.5 (1914: Sept. 1)
  - Item 6: The Tailor, 1914; Publication (Box 129, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.25:no.6 (1914: Sept. 8)
  - Item 7: The Tailor, 1914; Publication (Box 129, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.25:no.7 (1914: Sept. 15)
  - Item 8: The Tailor, 1914; Publication (Box 129, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.25:no.8 (1914: Sept. 22)
  - Item 9: The Tailor, 1914; Publication (Box 129, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.25:no.9 (1914: Sept. 29)
  - Item 10: The Tailor, 1914; Publication (Box 129, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.25:no.10 (1914: Oct. 6)
  - Item 11: The Tailor, 1914; Publication (Box 129, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.25:no.11 (1914: Oct. 13)
  - Item 12: The Tailor, 1914; Publication (Box 129, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.25:no.12 (1914: Oct. 20)
  - Item 13: The Tailor, 1914; Publication (Box 129, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.25:no.13 (1914: Oct. 27)
  - Item 14: The Tailor, 1914; Publication (Box 129, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.25:no.14 (1914: Nov. 2)
  - Item 15: The Tailor, 1914; Publication (Box 129, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.25:no.15 (1914: Nov. 9)
  - Item 16: The Tailor, 1914; Publication (Box 129, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.25:no.16 (1914: Nov. 16)
  - Item 17: The Tailor, 1914; Publication (Box 129, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.25:no.17 (1914: Nov. 23)
  - Item 18: The Tailor, 1914; Publication (Box 129, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.25:no.18 (1914: Nov. 30)
  - Item 19: The Tailor, 1914; Publication (Box 129, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.25:no.19 (1914: Dec. 8)
  - Item 20: The Tailor, 1914; Publication (Box 129, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.25:no.20 (1914: Dec. 15)
  - Item 21: The Tailor, 1914; Publication (Box 129, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.25:no.21 (1914: Dec. 22)
  - Item 22: The Tailor, 1914; Publication (Box 129, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.25:no.22 (1914: Dec. 29)
  - Item 23: The Tailor, 1915; Publication (Box 129, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.25:no.23 (1915: Jan. 5)
  - Item 24: The Tailor, 1915; Publication (Box 129, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.25:no.24 (1915: Jan. 12)
  - Item 25: The Tailor, 1915; Publication (Box 129, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.25:no.25 (1915: Jan. 19)
  - Item 26: The Tailor, 1915; Publication (Box 129, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.25:no.26 (1915: Jan. 26)
  - Item 27: The Tailor, 1915; Publication (Box 129, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.25:no.27 (1915: Feb. 2)
  - Item 28: The Tailor, 1915; Publication (Box 129, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.25:no.28 (1915: Feb. 9)
  - Item 29: The Tailor, 1915; Publication (Box 129, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.25:no.29 (1915: Feb. 16)
  - Item 30: The Tailor, 1915; Publication (Box 129, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.25:no.30 (1915: Feb. 23)
  - Item 31: The Tailor, 1915; Publication (Box 129, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.25:no.31 (1915: Mar. 2)
  - Item 32: The Tailor, 1915; Publication (Box 129, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.25:no.32 (1915: Mar. 9)
  - Item 33: The Tailor, 1915; Publication (Box 129, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.25:no.33 (1915: Mar. 16)
  - Item 34: The Tailor, 1915; Publication (Box 129, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.25:no.35 (1915: Mar. 30)
  - Item 35: The Tailor, 1915; Publication (Box 129, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.25:no.36 (1915: Apr. 6)
  - Item 36: The Tailor, 1915; Publication (Box 129, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.25:no.37 (1915: Apr. 13)
  - Item 37: The Tailor, 1915; Publication (Box 129, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.25:no.38 (1915: Apr. 20)
  - Item 38: The Tailor, 1915; Publication (Box 129, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.25:no.39 (1915: Apr. 27)
  - Item 39: The Tailor, 1915; Publication (Box 129, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.25:no.40 (1915: May 4)
  - Item 40: The Tailor, 1915; Publication (Box 129, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.25:no.41 (1915: May 11)
  - Item 41: The Tailor, 1915; Publication (Box 129, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.25:no.41 (1915: May 18). Should be be v.25:no.42.
  - Item 42: The Tailor, 1915; Publication (Box 129, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.25:no.43 (1915: May 25)
  - Item 43: The Tailor, 1915; Publication (Box 129, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.25:no.44 (1915: June 1)
  - Item 44: The Tailor, 1915; Publication (Box 129, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.25:no.45 (1915: June 8)
  - Item 45: The Tailor, 1915; Publication (Box 129, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.25:no.46 (1915: June 15)
  - Item 46: The Tailor, 1915; Publication (Box 129, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.25:no.47 (1915: June 22)
  - Item 47: The Tailor, 1915; Publication (Box 129, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.25:no.48 (1915: June 29)
  - Item 48: The Tailor, 1915; Publication (Box 129, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.25:no.49 (1915: July 7)
  - Item 49: The Tailor, 1915; Publication (Box 129, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.25:no.50 (1915: July 12)
  - Item 50: The Tailor, 1915; Publication (Box 129, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.25:no.51 (1915: July 20)
  - Item 51: The Tailor, 1915; Publication (Box 129, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.25:no.52 (1915: July 26)
  - Item 52: The Tailor, 1915; Publication (Box 129, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.25:no.53 (1915: Aug. 5)
  - Item 53: The Tailor, 1915; Publication (Box 129, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.25:no.54 (1915: Aug. 10)
  - Item 54: The Tailor, 1915; Publication (Box 129, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.25:no.55 (1915: Aug. 17)
  - Item 55: The Tailor, 1915; Publication (Box 129, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.25:no.56 (1915: Aug. 24)
- The Tailor, 1915-1916 (Box 129, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: The Tailor, 1915; Publication (Box 129, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.26:no.5 (1915: Aug. 31)
  - Item 2: The Tailor, 1915; Publication (Box 129, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.26:no.6 (1915: Sept. 7)
  - Item 3: The Tailor, 1915; Publication (Box 129, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.26:no.7 (1915: Sept. 14)
  - Item 4: The Tailor, 1915; Publication (Box 129, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.26:no.8 (1915: Sept. 21)
  - Item 5: The Tailor, 1915; Publication (Box 129, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.26:no.9 (1915: Sept. 28)
  - Item 6: The Tailor, 1915; Publication (Box 129, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.26:no.10 (1915: Oct. 5)
  - Item 7: The Tailor, 1915; Publication (Box 129, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.26:no.11 (1915: Oct. 12)
  - Item 8: The Tailor, 1915; Publication (Box 129, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.26:no.12 (1915: Oct. 19)
  - Item 9: The Tailor, 1915; Publication (Box 129, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.26:no.13 (1915: Oct. 26)
  - Item 10: The Tailor, 1915; Publication (Box 129, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.26:no.14 (1915: Nov. 2)
  - Item 11: The Tailor, 1915; Publication (Box 129, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.26:no.15 (1915: Nov. 9)
  - Item 12: The Tailor, 1915; Publication (Box 129, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.26:no.16 (1915: Nov. 16)
  - Item 13: The Tailor, 1915; Publication (Box 129, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.26:no.17 (1915: Nov. 23)
  - Item 14: The Tailor, 1915; Publication (Box 129, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.26:no.18 (1915: Nov. 30)
  - Item 15: The Tailor, 1915; Publication (Box 129, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.26:no.19 (1915: Dec. 7)
  - Item 16: The Tailor, 1915; Publication (Box 129, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.26:no.20 (1915: Dec. 14)
  - Item 17: The Tailor, 1915; Publication (Box 129, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.26:no.21 (1915: Dec. 21)
  - Item 18: The Tailor, 1915; Publication (Box 129, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.26:no.22 (1915: Dec. 28)
  - Item 19: The Tailor, 1916; Publication (Box 129, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.26:no.23 (1916: Jan. 4)
  - Item 20: The Tailor, 1916; Publication (Box 129, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.26:no.24 (1916: Jan. 11)
  - Item 21: The Tailor, 1916; Publication (Box 129, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.26:no.25 (1916: Jan. 18)
  - Item 22: The Tailor, 1916; Publication (Box 129, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.26:no.26 (1916: Jan. 25)
  - Item 23: The Tailor, 1916; Publication (Box 129, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.26:no.27 (1916: Feb. 1)
  - Item 24: The Tailor, 1916; Publication (Box 129, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.26:no.28 (1916: Feb. 8)
  - Item 25: The Tailor, 1916; Publication (Box 129, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.26:no.29 (1916: Feb. 15)
  - Item 26: The Tailor, 1916; Publication (Box 129, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.26:no.30 (1916: Feb. 22)
  - Item 27: The Tailor, 1916; Publication (Box 129, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.26:no.31 (1916: Feb. 29)
  - Item 28: The Tailor, 1916; Publication (Box 129, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.26:no.32 (1916: Mar. 7)
  - Item 29: The Tailor, 1916; Publication (Box 129, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.26:no.33 (1916: Mar. 14)
  - Item 30: The Tailor, 1916; Publication (Box 129, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.26:no.34 (1916: Mar. 21)
  - Item 31: The Tailor, 1916; Publication (Box 129, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.26:no.35 (1916: Mar. 28)
  - Item 32: The Tailor, 1916; Publication (Box 129, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.26:no.36 (1916: Apr. 4)
  - Item 33: The Tailor, 1916; Publication (Box 129, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.26:no.37 (1916: Apr. 11)
  - Item 34: The Tailor, 1916; Publication (Box 129, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.26:no.38 (1916: Apr. 18)
  - Item 35: The Tailor, 1916; Publication (Box 129, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.26:no.39 (1916: Apr. 25)
  - Item 36: The Tailor, 1916; Publication (Box 129, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.26:no.40 (1916: May 2)
  - Item 37: The Tailor, 1916; Publication (Box 129, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.26:no.41 (1916: May 9)
  - Item 38: The Tailor, 1916; Publication (Box 129, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.26:no.42 (1916: May 16)
  - Item 39: The Tailor, 1916; Publication (Box 129, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.26:no.43 (1916: May 23)
  - Item 40: The Tailor, 1916; Publication (Box 129, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.26:no.44 (1916: May 31)
  - Item 41: The Tailor, 1916; Publication (Box 129, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.26:no.45 (1916: June 6)
  - Item 42: The Tailor, 1916; Publication (Box 129, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.26:no.46 (1916: June 13)
  - Item 43: The Tailor, 1916; Publication (Box 129, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.26:no.47 (1916: June 20)
  - Item 44: The Tailor, 1916; Publication (Box 129, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.26:no.48 (1916: June 27)
  - Item 45: The Tailor, 1916; Publication (Box 129, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.26:no.49 (1916: July 5)
  - Item 46: The Tailor, 1916; Publication (Box 129, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.26:no.50 (1916: July 11)
  - Item 47: The Tailor, 1916; Publication (Box 129, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.26:no.51 (1916: July 18)
  - Item 48: The Tailor, 1916; Publication (Box 129, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.26:no.52 (1916: July 25)
- The Tailor, 1916-1917 (Box 129, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: The Tailor, 1916; Publication (Box 129, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.27:no.1 (1916: Aug. 1)
  - Item 2: The Tailor, 1916; Publication (Box 129, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.27:no.2 (1916: Aug. 8)
  - Item 3: The Tailor, 1916; Publication (Box 129, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.27:no.3 (1916: Aug. 15)
  - Item 4: The Tailor, 1916; Publication (Box 129, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.27:no.4 (1916: Aug. 22)
  - Item 5: The Tailor, 1916; Publication (Box 129, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.27:no.5 (1916: Aug. 29)
  - Item 6: The Tailor, 1916; Publication (Box 129, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.27:no.6 (1916: Sept. 5)
  - Item 7: The Tailor, 1916; Publication (Box 129, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.27:no.7 (1916: Sept. 12)
  - Item 8: The Tailor, 1916; Publication (Box 129, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.27:no.8 (1916: Sept. 19)
  - Item 9: The Tailor, 1916; Publication (Box 129, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.27:no.9 (1916: Sept. 26)
  - Item 10: The Tailor, 1916; Publication (Box 129, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.27:no.10 (1916: Oct. 3)
  - Item 11: The Tailor, 1916; Publication (Box 129, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.27:no.11 (1916: Oct. 10)
  - Item 12: The Tailor, 1916; Publication (Box 129, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.27:no.12 (1916: Oct. 17)
  - Item 13: The Tailor, 1916; Publication (Box 129, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.27:no.13 (1916: Oct. 24)
  - Item 14: The Tailor, 1916; Publication (Box 129, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.27:no.14 (1916: Oct. 31)
  - Item 15: The Tailor, 1916; Publication (Box 129, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.27:no.15 (1916: Nov. 7)
  - Item 16: The Tailor, 1916; Publication (Box 129, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.27:no.16 (1916: Nov. 14)
  - Item 17: The Tailor, 1916; Publication (Box 129, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.27:no.17 (1916: Nov. 21)
  - Item 18: The Tailor, 1916; Publication (Box 129, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.27:no.18 (1916: Nov. 28)
  - Item 19: The Tailor, 1916; Publication (Box 129, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.27:no.19 (1916: Dec. 5)
  - Item 20: The Tailor, 1916; Publication (Box 129, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.27:no.20 (1916: Dec. 12)
  - Item 21: The Tailor, 1916; Publication (Box 129, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.27:no.21 (1916: Dec. 19)
  - Item 22: The Tailor, 1916; Publication (Box 129, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.27:no.22 (1916: Dec. 26)
  - Item 23: The Tailor, 1917; Publication (Box 129, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.27:no.23 (1917: Jan. 2)
  - Item 24: The Tailor, 1917; Publication (Box 129, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.27:no.24 (1917: Jan. 9)
  - Item 25: The Tailor, 1917; Publication (Box 129, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.27:no.25 (1917: Jan. 16)
  - Item 26: The Tailor, 1917; Publication (Box 129, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.27:no.26 (1917: Jan. 23)
  - Item 27: The Tailor, 1917; Publication (Box 129, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.27:no.27 (1917: Jan. 30)
  - Item 28: The Tailor, 1917; Publication (Box 129, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.27:no.28 (1917: Feb. 6)
  - Item 29: The Tailor, 1917; Publication (Box 129, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.27:no.29 (1917: Feb. 13)
  - Item 30: The Tailor, 1917; Publication (Box 129, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.27:no.30 (1917: Feb. 20)
  - Item 31: The Tailor, 1917; Publication (Box 129, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.27:no.31 (1917: Feb. 27)
  - Item 32: The Tailor, 1917; Publication (Box 129, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.27:no.32 (1917: Mar. 6)
  - Item 33: The Tailor, 1917; Publication (Box 129, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.27:no.33 (1917: Mar. 13)
  - Item 34: The Tailor, 1917; Publication (Box 129, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.27:no.34 (1917: Mar. 20)
  - Item 35: The Tailor, 1917; Publication (Box 129, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.27:no.35 (1917: Mar. 27)
  - Item 36: The Tailor, 1917; Publication (Box 129, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.27:no.36 (1917: Apr. 3)
  - Item 37: The Tailor, 1917; Publication (Box 129, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.27:no.37 (1917: Apr. 10)
  - Item 38: The Tailor, 1917; Publication (Box 129, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.27:no.38 (1917: Apr. 17)
  - Item 39: The Tailor, 1917; Publication (Box 129, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.27:no.39 (1917: Apr. 24)
  - Item 40: The Tailor, 1917; Publication (Box 129, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.27:no.40 (1917: May 1)
  - Item 41: The Tailor, 1917; Publication (Box 129, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.27:no.41 (1917: May 8)
  - Item 42: The Tailor, 1917; Publication (Box 129, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.27:no.42 (1917: May 15)
  - Item 43: The Tailor, 1917; Publication (Box 129, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.27:no.43 (1917: May 22)
  - Item 44: The Tailor, 1917; Publication (Box 129, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.27:no.44 (1917: May 29)
  - Item 45: The Tailor, 1917; Publication (Box 129, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.27:no.45 (1917: June 5)
  - Item 46: The Tailor, 1917; Publication (Box 129, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.27:no.46 (1917: June 12)
  - Item 47: The Tailor, 1917; Publication (Box 129, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.27:no.47 (1917: June 19)
  - Item 48: The Tailor, 1917; Publication (Box 129, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.27:no.48 (1917: June 26)
  - Item 49: The Tailor, 1917; Publication (Box 129, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.27:no.49 (1917: July 3)
  - Item 50: The Tailor, 1917; Publication (Box 129, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.27:no.50 (1917: July 10)
  - Item 51: The Tailor, 1917; Publication (Box 129, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.27:no.51 (1917: July 17)
  - Item 52: The Tailor, 1917; Publication (Box 129, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.27:no.52 (1917: July 24)
- The Tailor, 1917-1918 (Box 129, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: The Tailor, 1917; Publication (Box 129, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.28:no.1 (1917: July 31)
  - Item 2: The Tailor, 1917; Publication (Box 129, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.28:no.2 (1917: Aug. 7)
  - Item 3: The Tailor, 1917; Publication (Box 129, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.28:no.3 (1917: Aug. 14)
  - Item 4: The Tailor, 1917; Publication (Box 129, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.28:no.4 (1917: Aug. 21)
  - Item 5: The Tailor, 1917; Publication (Box 129, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.28:no.5 (1917: Aug. 28)
  - Item 6: The Tailor, 1917; Publication (Box 129, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.28:no.6 (1917: Sept. 4)
  - Item 7: The Tailor, 1917; Publication (Box 129, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.28:no.7 (1917: Sept. 11)
  - Item 8: The Tailor, 1917; Publication (Box 129, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.28:no.8 (1917: Sept. 18)
  - Item 9: The Tailor, 1917; Publication (Box 129, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.28:no.9 (1917: Sept. 25)
  - Item 10: The Tailor, 1917; Publication (Box 129, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.28:no.10 (1917: Oct. 2)
  - Item 11: The Tailor, 1917; Publication (Box 129, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.28:no.11 (1917: Oct. 9)
  - Item 12: The Tailor, 1917; Publication (Box 129, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.28:no.12 (1917: Oct. 16)
  - Item 13: The Tailor, 1917; Publication (Box 129, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.28:no.13 (1917: Oct. 23)
  - Item 14: The Tailor, 1917; Publication (Box 129, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.28:no.14 (1917: Oct. 30)
  - Item 15: The Tailor, 1917; Publication (Box 129, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.28:no.15 (1917: Nov. 6)
  - Item 16: The Tailor, 1917; Publication (Box 129, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.28:no.16 (1917: Nov. 13)
  - Item 17: The Tailor, 1917; Publication (Box 129, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.28:no.17 (1917: Nov. 20)
  - Item 18: The Tailor, 1917; Publication (Box 129, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.28:no.19 (1917: Dec. 4)
  - Item 19: The Tailor, 1917; Publication (Box 129, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.28:no.20 (1917: Dec. 11)
  - Item 20: The Tailor, 1917; Publication (Box 129, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.28:no.21 (1917: Dec. 18)
  - Item 21: The Tailor, 1917; Publication (Box 129, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.28:no.22 (1917: Dec. 26)
  - Item 22: The Tailor, 1918; Publication (Box 129, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.28:no.23 (1918: Jan. 2)
  - Item 23: The Tailor, 1918; Publication (Box 129, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.28:no.24 (1918: Jan. 8)
  - Item 24: The Tailor, 1918; Publication (Box 129, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.28:no.25 (1918: Jan. 15)
  - Item 25: The Tailor, 1918; Publication (Box 129, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.28:no.26 (1918: Jan. 23)
  - Item 26: The Tailor, 1918; Publication (Box 129, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.28:no.27 (1918: Jan. 29)
  - Item 27: The Tailor, 1918; Publication (Box 129, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.28:no.28 (1918: Feb. 5)
  - Item 28: The Tailor, 1918; Publication (Box 129, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.28:no.29 (1918: Feb. 12)
  - Item 29: The Tailor, 1918; Publication (Box 129, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.28:no.30 (1918: Feb. 19)
  - Item 30: The Tailor, 1918; Publication (Box 129, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.28:no.31 (1918: Feb. 26)
  - Item 31: The Tailor, 1918; Publication (Box 129, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.28:no.32 (1918: Mar. 5)
  - Item 32: The Tailor, 1918; Publication (Box 129, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.28:no.33 (1918: Mar. 12)
  - Item 33: The Tailor, 1918; Publication (Box 129, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.28:no.34 (1918: Mar. 19)
  - Item 34: The Tailor, 1918; Publication (Box 129, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.28:no.35 (1918: Mar. 26)
  - Item 35: The Tailor, 1918; Publication (Box 129, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.28:no.36 (1918: Apr. 2)
  - Item 36: The Tailor, 1918; Publication (Box 129, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.28:no.37 (1918: Apr. 9)
  - Item 37: The Tailor, 1918; Publication (Box 129, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.28:no.38 (1918: Apr. 16)
  - Item 38: The Tailor, 1918; Publication (Box 129, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.28:no.39 (1918: Apr. 23)
  - Item 39: The Tailor, 1918; Publication (Box 129, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.28:no.40 (1918: Apr. 30)
  - Item 40: The Tailor, 1918; Publication (Box 129, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.28:no.41 (1918: May 7)
  - Item 41: The Tailor, 1918; Publication (Box 129, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.28:no.42 (1918: May 14)
  - Item 42: The Tailor, 1918; Publication (Box 129, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.28:no.43 (1918: May 21)
  - Item 43: The Tailor, 1918; Publication (Box 129, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.28:no.44 (1918: May 28)
  - Item 44: The Tailor, 1918; Publication (Box 129, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.28:no.45 (1918: June 4)
  - Item 45: The Tailor, 1918; Publication (Box 129, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.28:no.46 (1918: June 11)
  - Item 46: The Tailor, 1918; Publication (Box 129, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.28:no.47 (1918: June 18)
  - Item 47: The Tailor, 1918; Publication (Box 129, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.28:no.48 (1918: June 25)
  - Item 48: The Tailor, 1918; Publication (Box 129, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.28:no.49 (1918: July 2)
  - Item 49: The Tailor, 1918; Publication (Box 129, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.28:no.50 (1918: July 9)
  - Item 50: The Tailor, 1918; Publication (Box 129, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.28:no.51 (1918: July 16)
  - Item 51: The Tailor, 1918; Publication (Box 129, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.28:no.52 (1918: July 23)